This isn't the classroom.
It's right around the corner.
Go on. Let's go. Come.
Isn't that Ms. Seo?
Let me help you.
Don't you steal mine…
Ji-yeon. What's wrong?
Let me carry them.
But I need to go to class.
I have the mock exam tomorrow.
I'll take you to your class.
Do you know where it is?
Yes, I do.
Honey!
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
What's wrong?
What is wrong with her? Honey?
Hospital first, Min-woo.
Let's take her to the hospital.
I'll call you. Let me take her.
Let's go.
Wait.
Are you okay?
Where are we going?
I called Dr. Kim. We will--
Go home.
Hospital first. Let's do that, will you?
I just want to go home and rest. Later.
Ms. Seo's doctor said so,
and I did some research too.
If she stops taking it, she'll be okay.
It might take some time,
but she'll recover.
How can a person…
do such a thing?
He is her husband and her family.
We have to pretend we don't know.
Ms. Seo is very careful about it too.
I'm also looking into this.
We need more time.
What should I do?
Run the company soundly?
I want to rest.
Will you be okay by yourself?
Do you want to go home?
I'll call you later.
Okay.
Back then…
when you came to see me at the airport,
did you know about this?
Yes.
Okay.
IN-COMPANY BULLETIN BOARD
WHAT'S GOING ON IN JARIM?
IS IT TRUE THAT JARIM CEO HAS DEMENTIA?
MY SHARES…
This isn't right.
Let's go to the hospital.
I should've told you in advance.
Sometimes, these symptoms appear.
Then why didn't you tell me?
You should've gone to the hospital first.
Why did you suffer alone? This upsets me.
I did go to the hospital.
What did the doctor say?
Why is it happening to you?
It's the side effect of a drug.
The medicine I stopped taking
is the issue.
Was Ji-woo there too?
Her shoes were on me…
Oh, right. I need to call Ji-woo.
-Everyone was shocked.
-I'll do it.
JI-WOO
Anyway, what was that reporter
doing in the company?
I called him.
Why did you?
I had to find some info.
Honey, let me make this call first.
I was almost in trouble, wasn't I?
Yes.
If it hadn't been for Kyeong-do,
I would've kept taking that drug.
I avoided the crisis thanks to him.
Yes.
Are you mad?
No.
You must have been scared by yourself.
I had no idea
and insisted on going to England.
I tried to run away alone and save myself.
You must've been so frustrated back then.
Yes. I was so frustrated
that I threatened Kyeong-do.
Ji-yeon.
I'll be good. I'll do my best.
So don't be stressed.
You have to relax, sleep well,
and eat well to recover fast.
Trust me. You know what I'm capable of,
once I get into it.
I know. Dad used to say that.
"If Ji-woo really puts her mind to it,
even ten guys couldn't take her down."
-Ji-yeon.
-Yeah?
Divorce him.
Not yet.
How can you see that face every day?
I have no official reason
to divorce him yet.
He's such a diligent and sweet husband
on the outside.
So I'm waiting.
If I continue to drive him
into a corner, he'll fall.
INCOMING CALL
LEE KYEONG-DO
Don't blame Kyeong-do too much.
It was me who insisted.
I asked him not to say anything to you
until I tell you first.
I'm sure he was stressed about it too.
INCOMING CALL
MR. KIM
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Ji-woo must be sleeping.
The lights are off.
Maybe she's drinking? Shall I go check?
Ji-yeon was already here,
so she'll be fine.
You can relax and get some sleep.
Okay. Thank you.
No, I was here because I was worried.
-Bye now.
-Bye.
EPISODE 10
-Assistant Manager Lee.
-Yes.
Are things not going well in your life?
Everything's fine.
-You look completely run-down.
-No, I don't.
Hey,
come try tarot reading with me.
I found a place.
Good. Enjoy.
I'm interested.
Forget it. What does a rich boy
have to worry about?
Come on…
Assistant Manager,
a coffee?
Sure. Yes.
Kyeong-do, I got a call from An Da-hye.
What did she say?
That she has a question and wants to meet.
I'm so nervous.
Schedule a visit. Let's go.
I'll do it, but you go in alone.
She'd be upset and say nothing.
But I'm scared.
Hey, I heard it was a mess. Right?
Damn it.
What are you doing here?
So bitter. Hey, add some sweeteners.
Jeez, how many shots did you add to it?
Pain, pain, pain in the ass you are.
Wait, what do you mean? What mess?
JARIM. Your girlfriend's company.
-Just drink this.
-Hey.
I'm only checking the facts.
Are you writing about it?
What is it?
What's going on?
Hey, get out and get back to work.
You always leave me out.
The elders are talking. Get out.
-What…
-Now!
Okay, jeez.
Okay.
Before you write about it,
interview CEO Seo's doctor first.
So it's dementia?
I'll schedule an interview for you.
Get your facts straight.
You're acting like their son-in-law,
arranging a meeting with their doctor?
Hey, I'm not joking.
Okay, I heard you.
If this turns out well,
get me a job in the JARIM PR Team.
I'd be good at writing press releases.
You're out of your freaking mind.
Hey. Look, Mr. Lee.
Wait for me. Aren't you temperamental.
Mr. Lee!
It's a relief that you're doing well
in the company after joining.
I still have a long way to go.
Did you talk to your sister yesterday?
What did she say?
Be careful.
Act like you don't know anything yet.
She told me not to worry about her
and focus on the company,
consulting you if needed.
I told her to rest.
What's so important about the company?
I know.
What about Lucas? How are things going?
It's noisy in the company.
It won't settle until we have good energy.
The executives are murmuring about her.
If JARIM becomes dirt cheap
even before we know it…
Kang Min-woo has been planning
to sell the company for a long time.
He was the one
who informed about Cho Jin-eon.
That's what I'm worried about too.
It's not like I have any power.
They give me looks
since I'm known as the troublemaker.
I need your help, Min-woo.
We need to protect the company.
No need to mention it.
Anyway, don't worry too much, Ji-woo.
Keep calm, okay?
Yes.
If we bring Ro-a back,
wouldn't that help Ji-yeon relax?
There are good international schools
here too.
If Ro-a stays close to her, Ji-yeon will--
You've matured.
If you'd been like this sooner,
your sister wouldn't have been so stressed
and felt supported.
Better late than never. It's a good thing.
Sunny days come indeed.
My father-in-law would be happy.
INCOMING CALL
LEE KYEONG-DO
MISSED CALL
INCOMING CALL
LEE KYEONG-DO
Yes.
What about dinner? Have you eaten?
Just a little.
What about you?
Me too.
Are you disappointed in me?
I can't describe what I'm feeling.
I'm thankful but frustrated.
Sorry.
Where are you?
Here.
You're getting skinny.
You're skipping meals.
How long have you been there?
For some time after I got off work.
Kyeong-do.
I don't know what this feeling is.
You protected my sister for me
when I was wandering.
But why did the incident at the airport
come to my mind, so selfishly?
"Maybe Kyeong-do didn't stop me for love."
"Was he forced because Ji-yeon asked him?"
This is no time to think about that.
Aren't I so selfish?
To have those thoughts?
You know what, Ji-woo?
When I went to meet you at the airport,
I was thinking,
"Ji-woo's sister's illness
is giving me an excuse."
Otherwise, I didn't have
any other excuse to stop you.
"I have no choice but to stop Seo Ji-woo."
Aren't I damn selfish
to have that thought?
But at the time, nothing mattered.
"Only if you don't leave."
"Now that you're single again..."
"Only if you stay close to me."
That's all I could think about.
If that's not love,
what is?
Hold me.
I was scared.
You have me.
I'm right here.
I'm only performing on weekdays.
It's a big theater.
My goodness.
Playing the lead role in such a big show?
My Cha Woo-sik is playing the lead role?
Three people are taking turns to perform,
and I just do once or twice a week.
Still, it's a lead role.
Being kind pays off.
You're finally getting paid.
That reminds me. The pay.
Playing Godot should pay a lot.
Let's get a new bed for Dong-won.
What about the money you got
for painting Ji-woo?
I bought your mother a necklace with that.
Ten don of pure gold.
Her friends are wearing something heavy
or whatever.
She even gave us a building.
I can do that for her.
That's the kind of daughter-in-law I am.
Right.
Why won't it come off?
Woo-sik. Cha Woo-sik?
Is it gone?
Did you spend it all?
When you're a father and a breadwinner?
Well…
Se-yeong, there was something
I really wanted.
So I bought it.
What did you buy?
Something on home shopping.
Did you buy the TV in the end?
Wait. No. Wait. That's not it. Wait.
Wait. Give me a second. Let me find it.
What is it?
DA NANG FAMILY PACKAGE TOUR
5 NIGHTS 7 DAYS SPECIAL PRICE
-Vietnam?
-It's just…
I mean, we should travel abroad too, no?
This building came with the loan,
so you had such a hard time paying it off.
I worked part-time doing delivery and all
and never brought a decent paycheck.
Our poor Dong-won.
Let's give him a chance
to take a passport photo this time.
Se-yeong?
I'm sorry. Don't cry.
This is all my fault.
I'll cancel it. I can get a refund.
I swear I can have my money back, okay?
Honey!
Yes.
Good job!
Thank you!
This is why I love you.
You're so cool.
Oh, gosh, Se-yeong. Thank you so much.
I mean, it's not refundable,
so I was so scared.
-I was worried to death.
-Dong-won.
Dong-won, come here.
-My baby.
-Let's go travel.
-Dong-won, the passport…
Why are you crying?
CORRECTIONAL CENTER
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
You followed along?
I have nothing to say to you, but…
I have some questions.
Like what?
Why did you want to meet
Reporter Kim Doo-jin?
Why do you want to know?
You know Kang Min-woo, right?
Of course.
He's Cho Jin-eon's brother-in-law.
I want to know what's between you two.
What does it look like to you?
Let me rephrase the question.
Why do you think he reported
what's between you and Cho Jin-eon?
Is it okay for a reporter
to reveal the informant?
I didn't know he was the informant.
I received it by mail--
I found out through another route.
Do you know him well?
No.
We've only said hi.
Maybe we met once or twice.
But that's funny.
Who the hell does that fucker think he is,
tipping off the press about me?
If you were just curious
about the informant,
then you don't need
Reporter Kim anymore, right?
Reporter Lee.
Yes.
All I'm asking for is one thing.
I can't wait to get out of here.
Why the hell am I stuck in here
when Cho Jin-eon is on probation?
I'm not the only one who did drugs.
Who's going to get me out of here?
Cho Jin-eon won't answer his phone.
So I thought I should find the informant
through the reporter and screw him up.
But then,
what could I possibly do
when I couldn't even reach him?
So you knew
Kang Min-woo was the informant,
and you needed Reporter Kim to confirm.
Oh my. Is that what I said?
The reporters always catch me so easily.
Even in my prime.
You already contacted Kang Min-woo,
but he's not answering.
What do you want to know?
Why would you want
to screw Kang Min-woo up?
The reason you chose him
as the rope to get you out of here,
the dangerous reason for him to do that...
That's what I want.
There is no dangerous reason to do that,
Reporter Lee.
Let's say there is.
Like a movie, let's say there is.
Then are you going to save me
instead of Kang Min-woo?
The court will sentence you
according to the law.
You have nothing.
You have no power. You have no backup.
Unless you have a good card, don't come.
I also have a routine.
It's hard to kill each day
of my sentence in here.
Didroxin.
Kang Min-woo will react to that.
Didroxin? So is that a button
that will trigger Kang Min-woo?
It began with the article I wrote.
"JARIM CEO's Alzheimer's…"
It's not Alzheimer's.
Kyeong-do, this is quite serious.
How far are you planning to go?
Where that asshole is going.
I have to be there first.
ECONOMICS TEAM
MA SUNG-CHEOL
Hey.
Hey, did you read the article?
I was working. I'll read it soon.
Did you make it good?
You're not even my department manager.
How dare you check--
-Find the article.
-Okay.
JARIM CEO SEO JI-YEON
'DIDROXIN'S TEMPORARY SIDE EFFECT'
NO ISSUE IN MANAGEMENT
Dementia?
If you take Didroxin wrong,
you get dementia?
Yes. Right.
Seo Ji-yeon?
From JARIM Apparel?
No shit.
He's one hell of an asshole. Listen.
Send him one more quick delivery.
This time, put it as…
"Didroxin, a visit requested."
As simple as that.
Yoo Dan-bi didn't post it herself.
Her friend posted it, and she tagged her.
Compared to last year,
the budget on her posts is different.
She obviously has more money.
Anything else that stands out?
Well, it seems she's posting
less than before.
She's clearly aware of something.
How about her routine after work?
She's really into Pilates.
But she always has a drink
after her class.
Then what's the point of all that?
She goes to her regular places
on a random basis.
-By herself?
-No.
She's an insider.
With new faces almost every time.
Here.
Eat. When you have low sugar,
you have no energy.
But don't you think this is wrong
at ten o'clock at night?
Eat with a sense of duty
as if JARIM's future relies on your arms.
Here.
Good girl.
How's Ji-yeon doing?
Mother, you don't need to worry too much.
Ji-yeon is the same as usual.
You've read the article.
The illness doesn't get that serious.
How's the atmosphere at work?
The noise died down when we said
it was the side effect of a drug.
Only you're still sensitive about it.
It'll make you ill.
Excuse me. Let me make a quick call.
Yes, go ahead.
Hey. When did you get here?
Just now.
What were you doing in Mom's room?
Well, I was wondering
if we had to change her bathroom tiles.
She said they were slippery.
Did she?
How come you pay less attention than me
when you're her daughter? Let's go.
Go ahead.
I'm here with Ji-woo.
Ji-woo too? Hurry up.
I have a meeting, so I have to get going.
Okay.
I was going to keep it
between Ji-woo and me until I settle it.
What has this man done to you?
Before that…
I think he is going to...
disclose our mother-daughter story.
What story?
About Ji-woo?
That she's not Dad's biological child?
He's going to disclose that?
I think so.
We might as well get ready for it.
Why is he going that far?
I end up
tying you down.
How can you sue me? I'm hurt.
Min-woo,
buying and selling JARIM requires
a lot more than buying a corner store.
Right.
Nothing guarantees
that Aaron invests it in JARIM.
I know.
Then why do you keep putting it off?
You show no action.
I need to find a way to live as well.
You think 30 billion won is a joke?
The stock market's fluctuating
because Seo Ji-woo recruited Lucas.
JARIM will never be for sale.
You're right.
I never thought Seo Ji-woo would help.
-Min-woo.
-Jun-soo.
Bae Jun-soo.
The stock market is fluctuating.
JARIM's value went up.
So if it's on the market,
everyone will be eager to buy it.
Even without Aaron's fund,
people will bite it.
Then you need to butter me up,
not fucking sue me.
Are you sure it's even on the market?
Does Seo Ji-yeon agree to sell it?
She's not going to, obviously.
I'll have to make her agree to it!
I'm busy working on that,
that's why I'm having fucking raw fish
instead of a proper meal!
Seo Ji-woo,
she's not Chairman Seo's daughter.
I was busy
sending the DNA test today, buddy.
Seo Ji-yeon's dementia,
Seo Ji-woo being an illegitimate child...
That creates a management risk.
I talked to Executive Director Choi.
Once the article on Ji-woo is released,
Seo Ji-woo will be kicked out.
Then Seo Ji-yeon will stagger.
Whatever Seo Ji-yeon says,
you think people will listen?
But how can you do the DNA test
when your father's deceased? Are you sure?
I looked it up.
A DNA test of the sisters and the mother
shows that they have different fathers.
I'm okay, but I'm worried about Mom.
The company would come after me too.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yes. Well…
My phone will be on fire,
and I'll be bombarded with texts.
Like when my divorce news got out.
It'll get quiet after some time.
Kang Min-woo won't let this slide.
Let's get ahead of him.
I swear Kang Min-woo will play a game.
And if it's going to happen,
whoever plays it first wins.
But then you…
You're smart.
You did earn the Assistant Manager title.
Sit down.
Let me just borrow a pen.
-Hey, that's mine.
-Come on.
Let me use it just this once…
Hey, you're here.
Hello.
Have you had coffee yet?
We also have Job's tears tea.
Coffee, please. Iced.
Assistant Manager Lee.
Two iced Americanos.
Come with me.
-Three iced Americanos.
-What?
-First time visiting a press company?
-Yes, it's interesting.
The Entertainment Team
is at the end of the hall.
This is the Politics Team.
The Current Affairs Team's there.
This way.
-But…
-That means, "Know when to join."
Aren't you getting coffee?
Yes, sir.
But why…
Wait. What?
Gosh…
I'd like you to write the article.
Me?
The temperature of your words
would be different.
Being not so fond of me
is also a sign of interest.
In a way it would induce sympathy, please.
People wouldn't pity you for that.
Just show yourself as you are.
Just as I am?
Yes.
Sounds good.
Please write it as a special article.
A couple of photos on it would be better.
Okay, sure. In terms of the photos…
You're not using random photos
on the internet…
are you?
What is he, a dog that needs to poop?
Damn it.
I'll find a photographer.
I can do it today.
Would you like to go to the salon?
It'll take some time.
Sure, thank you.
Thank you. For giving us an article.
You'll get explosive views for sure.
An illegitimate child out of wedlock.
It's a nice keyword.
I'll see you later.
Yes, sure.
Take care. I'll see you later.
Bye. Thank you for the coffee.
So you'd just meet her directly?
It's too big for a mere assistant manager.
Hey. I'm the legend
of Dongwoon Daily's Entertainment Team.
Says who?
Why is she smiling like that?
Wait, this is good. I like the third one.
It's perfect with the breeze.
My goodness.
Even like that, she's pretty.
So brazenly pretty.
When did you first find out about that?
I was 28.
And you hadn't noticed it until then?
No.
That's how my father was.
Perhaps, he loved me more than my sister.
When you found out,
you must've had a lot on your mind.
A lot…
I did have a lot on my mind.
How should I put it?
Should I say I seemed ridiculous?
I didn't deserve everything
I took for granted.
That sense of self-destruction.
Everything around me,
the people and the environment...
I became ashamed toward them all.
So back then, I ran away.
From everything.
Ever since then, have you talked
to your father, mother, or your sister?
No.
When I was running away to the US,
my father and I talked
about this and that at the airport.
Though we were talking about other things,
the message was "thank you",
"I love you" and "I appreciate you".
It's only very recently
that I had the talk with my mother.
This interview,
it must have not been an easy decision,
not only for you, but for her as well.
Yet she still agreed to it.
If you say no, I won't do it.
It'll be out anyway.
Kang Min-woo, that man,
even had the DNA test done.
Although this is my doing,
how can I live with that?
How am I going to live with my head up?
But…
it was hard on me.
I had such a hard time back then.
Your dad was so crazy about work
that I barely saw him.
I was stuck in a house as big as a palace.
I could barely eat.
I felt like dying.
I didn't run away to Paris to do that.
While I was living there, it just…
It happened…
You know what?
What tortured me was…
not your choice.
It was that you turned your guilt
into blame toward me.
I was completely in the dark.
And you hated me…
so much…
That's what tortured me.
My life,
it's coming to a close.
But you…
Are you going to be okay?
Yes.
It won't be so effective.
Because I've never been okay.
Perhaps, you could've kept it a secret
within your family.
I'd like to ask you the reason
you accepted this interview.
Before my father passed away,
he always wanted me to help him
with the company work.
I thought it would be shameless of me,
so I kept running away from it.
But now, it's time to help my sister,
CEO Seo Ji-yeon.
And working hard for JARIM Apparel
is a way to repay his kindness.
Revealing and explaining my situation
would be the start of all that.
Very well.
HER FATHER
WHO RAISED HER WITH HEART
FOCUSING ON JARIM TO REPAY FATHER'S LOVE
LATE CHAIRMAN'S LOVE, JARIM'S ROOT
THIS IS A NEW SIDE OF SEO JI-WOO
BUT IT'S STILL SHOCKING!
SHE SOUNDS RELIABLE LOL - SHE'S HONEST
LOOKING FORWARD TO SEO JI-WOO'S PATH
JARIM'S SECOND DAUGHTER
THE SECRET OF HER BIRTH
DNA EVALUATION - SUSPECTED
TO NOT SHARE A BIOLOGICAL FATHER
She's playing smart.
On vacation?
They went abroad when there's an incident?
Who am I supposed to have makgeolli with?
Damn it.
Hey, it's Kyeong-do.
What?
Hey, Kyeong-do,
-what are you doing here?
-Hello.
What's that?
I knew it.
You're all down, ruining your beauty.
-What is that RV?
-What do you think?
It's the pumpkin carriage to pick you up.
Hey, hop in.
That's awesome.
Mr. Kim, good night.
-Ji-woo's not eaten yet. She needs to eat.
-Okay.
-Goodnight.
-Drive safe.
Come here.
Is it your first time?
Yes. Where did you get this? Whose is it?
Who cares? What matters is that
we're using it right now. Just enjoy.
Do you have a license for it?
Can you drive something this big?
I have a license.
Anyway, where are we going?
I'm dead tired.
You can rest.
We have a bed and a shower booth.
I'll cook. Nothing to stress about.
Why are you so excited?
You didn't even come.
I was busy.
I bought some light to hang outside.
I got stuff for the barbecue.
Tteokbokki, ramyeon, I got everything.
I was busy. So busy.
Can you even finish it today?
No, I connected it.
Maybe the light's broken.
I tested it at home, but I was in a rush.
I'm hungry. Let's have ramyeon.
Why have ramyeon when we have barbecue?
Ramyeon is for dessert.
Sit here and get some rest.
You'll see my fire-building skill. Sit.
Hey, it's burning.
Or not.
I feel like someone's watching me.
Maybe that's why.
We can have the meat for dessert.
Right. We shouldn't be so narrow-minded.
I think our ancestors
came up with good proverbs.
If it's to diss me, stop.
"Hunger is the best side dish."
A proverb like that is so fit.
Don't you think that's poetic?
The tea smells nice.
It's from England. You like England.
I think it's getting a little chilly--
Here.
Wasn't it tough?
Well… It's just…
Just a little. It was a little tough.
You had a nice outfit.
Were you there?
Our Ji-woo looks great in anything.
I stopped by for a second.
To see how you were doing.
You should've come to say hi.
Because I felt bad.
For asking you to do that.
I felt bad, so I couldn't say hi.
Idiot, why would you feel bad?
I'm thankful.
Thank you, Kyeong-do.
I'm embarrassed.
Then…
how about a kiss?
Shall we?
Thank you.
Hey, this is crazy.
What would you do without me?
Here.
I'm still sleepy.
Give me a piggyback.
I think that will wake me up.
I can't do that on an empty stomach.
Why not? You carried Bella Jin.
That was for business.
You and I,
we need to cherish each other.
No strength training on an empty stomach.
Here we go.
Nice.
I think I need to stay like this
for ten more minutes.
Ten minutes?
Sure.
Gosh, do they think
they're filming a movie?
Who goes to work from here?
Mr. Kim!
Good morning!
You're laughing? How can you be laughing?
Still, Kyeong-do is the only one
who makes Ji-woo laugh.
Thank you.
It was nice. Thank you.
What is he getting out of?
Lee Kyeong-do, what's going on?
What is it?
What was that RV for?
Did you cover someone big?
To make me happy?
No. I was just trying to see
what it's like to come to work in an RV.
-You rode an RV for no reason?
-Yes.
What does an RV have to do
with covering someone big?
Once upon a time,
Lee Kyeong-do actually worked really hard.
When Actor Ha Min-su was in his prime, no
one could cover for him. He was so busy.
Then Lee Kyeong-do rented an RV.
He basically kidnapped him,
giving him a ride from Seoul to Busan.
Apparently, he was so touched
by Kyeong-do's effort that he said yes.
What do you think he did during that time?
He gave the actor beers to gather a scoop.
You and your petty tricks.
Petty? Come here, you asshole.
No…
You know what's more amazing?
Ha Min-su bought that RV.
-Exactly.
-Since then,
he drove the RV to the set.
Assistant Manager, you got good money
from the RV company?
I'm not like you.
Yet, you have nothing today?
I gathered news about myself. "Who am I?"
Are you shitting with your mouth?
We never get along. I do respect you,
but we don't get along at all.
Think again. We do get along.
-We don't.
-We totally do.
We totally don't.
Gosh, I don't get along with any of you.
The maeuntang here
is your favorite, right?
My father told me.
He often offered to have soju here.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Help yourself.
No wonder you're a regular here.
I assume you have something to say.
I think you already know.
Things are getting serious
between the executives.
The employees will talk about it
and stop eventually,
but the stockholders won't.
The executives and the stockholders,
I'm asking you to reassure them.
I know you can do that.
I can.
But, Ms. Seo,
I'm not exactly comfortable
with this situation either.
My father wouldn't have been
comfortable either
when you siphoned MANZAAR's designer
to launch a new brand.
I know about that too.
When my father was in the hospital,
he told me about that incident.
He buried it without letting executives
or stockholders know, you know?
He said,
"She'll help you out at least once."
It's time for that one chance.
Excuse me.
One soju, please.
At the time,
he didn't even say he was disappointed.
That's how he was.
Chairman Seo Won-seok.
Only this time.
If there is any issue
with Director Seo Ji-woo again,
your safety may not be guaranteed either.
That's the atmosphere right now.
Pour me a glass too.
Thank you.
I guess that's when.
What's when?
When you were hurt,
Ji-woo must've found out then.
Maybe that's why she left.
Still, she grew up to be a bright person.
Yes.
Should we invite her for dinner?
Kyeong-do will hate it.
-Right?
-Yeah.
You should've told me
that you were coming my house.
I didn't know they invited you too.
A son isn't a guest to invite.
A guest would come when they're invited.
You're normally at the laundromat.
Here. Eat.
Thank you. I absolutely love yukgaejang.
Enjoy.
Yes. Thank you for the food.
Craving soju?
People make that sound
when they have spicy food.
You see, this is the exact taste
that I expected when I first saw it.
You should have opened a restaurant
instead of a laundromat.
Thank you for the food.
Bulgogi too? Thank you.
Can I have this bulgogi too?
As much as you want.
So full. Gosh.
Here.
That was a nice meal.
ON MUTE
-Baseball now?
-Well,
I muted it.
Stop watching baseball.
Now is so not the time.
You see…
What?
Well… in my opinion…
Quitting what you like, whatever it is…
Well… it's crazy tough.
Still, baseball isn't harmful.
That's nice.
It's healthy. It prevents dementia.
Really?
Better than Go-Stop?
Why, Go-Stop has a risk of gambling.
Yes. You're right.
-It's a hit.
-What, really?
What's the point of the other team's hit?
Are you a Hanyeong fan?
Have you seen them losing by 7-nil
then turning it around by 8 to 7?
No. Unfortunately, I missed it.
Do you like baseball?
Kind of.
-We have something in common.
-Of course.
Let me give you a piece of apple.
-I didn't peel it though.
-Thank you.
Maybe if Seo Ji-yeon
was born out of wedlock...
But Seo Ji-woo? And get rid of her?
That won't affect the management.
That's too weak. That won't do it.
A KO isn't the only way to win.
You can also win by decision.
Do you know
what Koreans are most sensitive about?
Affairs.
JARIM's dead Chairman Seo's wife
had an affair.
And her daughter also has an affair.
I think this alley is pretty. It's cozy.
Maybe it's true that a married couple
has similar taste.
You're copying me.
Don't go overboard.
Okay.
I like how it sounds.
Alley.
Alleyway.
Alley captain.
Alley entrance.
You should've stayed in the Culture Team.
You know what?
It feels weird
to have dinner together like this.
Why?
Is it like visiting your in-laws' house?
No.
I mean I like it.
It's nice.
It's like an alley. A cozy alley.
Let's live like this alley.
JARIM's dead Chairman Seo's wife
had an affair.
And her daughter also has an affair.
There will be a boycott of JARIM.
It'll only be a matter of time
until the sisters get kicked out.
And the company will be sold.
So, you are… going?
Don't you know what this field is like?
It's better to hide. We might as well die!
Just go live abroad.
-Director Seo Ji-woo.
-Director Seo,
don't you think that's irresponsible?
Then let her live as an adulteress!
I'm here
because the dog was barking too loud.
Kang Min-woo,
you're out of bullets, right?
I'll go, and if I can't bear it,
I'll come back.
Ji-woo, let's…
live well.